Okay, you have your two to three SMART goals.
Now we build the action plan.
This is where you use your 90-Day Way Core 4 scorecard.
The 90 day plan is rooted in your M.V.P. and values.
It incorporates both your professional
and personal priorities.
For each goal, your plan guides you
to ask four critical questions.
First, what daily or weekly actions are required?
Break the goal into concrete steps.
Second, what resources are needed?
Is it time, money, introductions,
a specific piece of information?
Third, who is in your corner?
An athlete does not train alone.
They build an ecosystem of accountability.
This requires creating alignment on multiple fronts.
With your manager, what conversations do you need to have
to get their support and buy in?
With your team, how will you communicate your goals
so they can support the vision?
And with your loved ones at home,
what do they need to know
to be a part of your support system?
Think about the right cadence for check-ins
with each of these groups to keep them engaged,
but also to keep yourself on track.
And finally, what is the deadline?
How will you celebrate?
Deadlines drive execution.
And celebrating as an outcome, even if it's a small win,
is what builds the positive momentum
that makes you want to tackle the next goal.
It's a crucial part of your wellbeing and resilience.
This plan is a living document.
It's flexible.
It gives you direction, but it also allows you to pivot
when the unexpected happens.
In your playbook, you'll use the template
to build out your first 90-day plan
for each of your SMART goals.
This is your roadmap for the next three months.